# Michael Ryan Palmer

101 Halloran Dr. Breesport NY, 14816

E-mail: Palmermr20@mounties.mansfield.edu Phone: 607-731-7630

# **Summary**

I am adaptable, quick learning, hardworking, and a motivated individual. I am very interested in the IT Internship StateFarm has to offer and believe it will help me better myself. I'm hoping this will be a great leaning experience. I believe my skills as well as my go to attitude will be helpful to StateFarm.

## Skillset

Netbeans, Java, Html5, CSS, STS, Adobe Products, AutoCad

## **Education**

Mansfield University of Pennsylvania, Mansfield, PA Bachelor of Computer Information Science **May 2019 (anticipated)** 3.49/4.00 GPA

**Corning Community College, Corning, NY** 

**Summer 2011- Spring 2013** 

Gst Boces, Horseheads, NY

Licensed for Adobe Products and Software

**Sept. 2008 – June 2010** 

## **Work Experience**

T-shirt Studio, Horseheads, NY

**Summer 2014-Present** 

## Associate/ Graphic Design

- Designing custom graphics and decals for customers, as well as print on t-shirts.
- Provide associate duties, including operating a register and clean-up, as well as operating a Roland vinyl cutter and heat press

## Spencer's, Horseheads, NY

**Summer 2014-Present** 

### Associate

- Upselling and greeting people in the store.
- Operating the register and collecting emails
- Cleanup as well as store movement(moving products around the shop)
- Keeping track of store inventory

### Papa John's, Elmira Heights, NY

Fall 2013 - Fall 2014

#### Driver/Insider

- Delivery driver for food based products as well as promotions
- Working in a team based environment to get the product out on time
- Making food up to the standard of Papa John's
- Sanitary cleanup

# Michael Ryan Palmer

101 Halloran Dr. Breesport NY, 14816

E-mail: Palmermr20@mounties.mansfield.edu Phone: 607-731-7630

## ACC, Elmira, NY

## **Spring 2013- Fall 2013**

## Information Gatherer

- Talking on a phone from a random computer generated number and giving out free magazines for information about the company/business
- Tracking down people of interest, then handling argumentative and challenging those people of interest, like a CIO or a CTO of State Farm or Walmart.

## UPS Store, Horseheads & Corning, NY

### **Spring 2012- Spring 2013**

#### Associate

- Shipping valuable products to various parts of the world
- Packaging those products so they do not get damaged
- Customer service and claims

# **Activities/Organizations**

**CIS Club-** Mansfield University, Mansfield, PA **MUTT-** Mansfield University, Mansfield, PA

Sept. 2015- Present Sept. 2015- Present

## **References**

Excellent references available on request.